<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telekom Innovation Laboratories</title>
    <description>Telekom Innovation Laboratories (T-Labs) are the central research and development unit of Deutsche Telekom AG</description>
    <link>https://TelekomLabs.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 15:44:15 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 15:44:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hardening Framework</title>
        <description>The goal of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://hardening.io&quot;&gt;Hardening Framework&lt;/a&gt; is simply to create a common layer for hardening operating systems and services easily and without interference. Even if you aren&#39;t knee-deep in configuration manuals for services or the latest security recommendations, you will be able to implement and use this framework with ease.</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://TelekomLabs.github.io/security/2015/07/15/hardening-framework/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://TelekomLabs.github.io/security/2015/07/15/hardening-framework/</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefox Os</title>
        <description>The prevalent operating systems used for today&#39;s smartphones have one thing in common&amp;#58; they are designed to function as &quot;closed&quot; operating systems. Neither users nor network operators can make any independent decisions that would impact the services used – they must accept the structures as defined by the developers. One way to solve this dilemma would be the consequent use of open standards such as HTML5 and the migration of key functionalities into the cloud. That is why Telekom has established a partnership with the Mozilla Foundation, which develops such a system for smartphones with Boot to Gecko (Firefox OS). The &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/svic&quot;&gt;Labs are making important contributions&lt;/a&gt; to this project when it comes to device security and the development of a unique user interface.</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://TelekomLabs.github.io/mobile%20os/2015/07/13/firefox-os/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://TelekomLabs.github.io/mobile%20os/2015/07/13/firefox-os/</guid>
        
        
        <category>mobile os</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Honeypot</title>
        <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://dtag-dev-sec.github.io/&quot;&gt;Deutsche Telekom&#39;s honeypot project&lt;/a&gt; was started in 2010 by a small group of enthusiasts. We initially started with Lukas Rist&#39;s great Glastopf web honeypot and soon added further honeypot daemons like kippo, honeytrap and dionaea. Over the next years we deployed more and more honeypots.</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://TelekomLabs.github.io/security/2015/07/12/honeypot/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://TelekomLabs.github.io/security/2015/07/12/honeypot/</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
